One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Wealth, fame, power...
‫الثروة والصيت والقوة،‬
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, obtained everything the world has to offer.
‫الرجل الذي نال كل ما في هذا العالم، ملك القراصنة غولد روجر‬
What he said in his final moments drove countless souls to the seas.
‫أجَّج قوله قبيل موته اندفاع الناس إلى البحار‬
You want my treasure?
‫كنزي؟ إنه لكم إن أردتموه‬
Find it!
‫ابحثوا عنه، تركت كلَّ شيءٍ في ذلك المكان!‬
People set their sights on the Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams.
‫شدّ الرجال رحالهم نحو الغراند لاين مطاردين أحلامهم‬
The world has truly entered the Great Pirate Era!
‫العالم الآن يعيش عصر القراصنة العظيم‬
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
‫أحلامنا جمعناها فيما بيننا‬
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
‫قاصدين البحث عما نريد الحصول عليه‬
One Piece! ONE PIECE
‫ون بيس‬
Compasses? Not for me. Left them all behind Rashinban nante juutai no moto
‫ما كانت البوصلة لتأتي لنا سوى بالتأخير‬
I'm headed out to sea, with my heart serving as guide Netsu ni ukasare kaji wo toru no sa
‫نمضي في طريقنا بهمة المشاعر المشتعلة‬
Following the ancient map to the spot marked "X" reveals Hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
‫وخريطة الكنز القديمة التي يعلوها التراب‬
Yeah, it's only legendary till someone proves it's real Tashikameta no nara densetsu janai!
‫لن تكون محض قصة خرافية إن تبينا صحتها‬
When the world's got you down,
‫وإن هبت بداخلك عواصف هوجاء‬
Their biorhythm will carry you through BIORHYTHM nokkatte
‫فتمايل على إيقاع الآخرين حولك‬
We're gonna make the most of it Omoi sugoseba ii!
‫وتجاهل وجودها‬
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
‫أحلامنا جمعناها فيما بيننا‬
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
‫قاصدين البحث عما نريد الحصول عليه‬
Got some change to my name, POCKET no COIN
‫عملة أحفظها في جيبي‬
and maybe you wanna be my friend? Soreto YOU WANNA BE MY FRIEND?
‫وهل تريد أن تكون صديقي؟‬
We are, we are on the cruise! WE ARE, WE ARE ON THE CRUISE!
‫نحن، نحن نخوض مغامرة‬
WE ARE!
‫نحن‬
Alright.
‫اسمعوا، سيهاجمون من هذا الساحل عند الفجر‬
and that the only route into the village from here is this slope.
‫والطريق الوحيد إلى الجزيرة هو هذا المنحدر‬
The cliffs are too steep everywhere else.
‫الباقي كلّه جروف، ممّا يعني أنهم لن يستطيعوا اجتيازها‬
The Slope
‫المنحدر‬
In other words, if we defend this slope at all costs,
‫بعبارة أخرى، إن تمكنّا من من تأمين هذا المنحدر،‬
the village will be safe!
‫فلن يطال القرية اعتداء!‬
Oh! That's easy!
‫فهمت، هذا بسيط!‬
It's easy to say, but we still have to fight!
‫الكلام سهل، الباقي يعتمد على قوتنا‬
What can you guys do?
‫ماذا تجيدون؟‬
Cut.
‫التقطيع‬
Stretch.
‫التمدد‬
Steal.
‫السرقة‬
I can hide.
‫أما أنا فأجيد الاختباء‬
– You're gonna fight!
‫ستقاتل!‬
I was just kidding, c'mon!
‫وحيكم، إني أمزح!‬
Oh, Klahadore!
‫كلاهادور-سان!‬
Welcome back!
‫مرحبًا بعودتك!‬
How is Miss Kaya?
‫كيف حال الآنسة؟‬
She's resting now.
‫إنّها نائمة‬
The whole affair really wore her out...
‫بدت في غاية التعب...‬
To think such a thing happened while I was in the neighboring town...
‫كيف لذلك أن يحدث أثناء ذهابي للبلدة المجاورة...‬
That Usopp boy certainly is a troublemaker.
‫ذاك الصبي أوسوب مزعج حقًّا.‬
Indeed...
‫أجل...‬
And claiming you were a pirate of all things…
‫وعلاوة على كلّ هذا، ادعى أنّك قرصان...‬
It's not even a good lie!
‫ما أغباها من كذبة!‬
Is that so...?
‫صحيح.‬
What is this?
‫ما هذه؟‬
Oh, that is a present from the miss to you.
‫إنها هدية لك من الآنسة.‬
She said it's your third year at the mansion,
‫بذكرى سنتك الثالثة في هذا القصر،‬
so it's a sort of commemoration.
‫لذا فإنّه احتفال تذكاري.‬
A commemoration...
‫احتفال تذكاري...‬
Your current glasses seem to slip often,
‫نظارتك الحالية تنزلق كثيرًا،‬
so she custom-ordered those!
‫لذا فقد طلبت هذه لتُصمم خصيصًا لك،‬
She's such a nice, thoughtful person!
‫يا للطفها ومراعاتها!‬
A commemoration, you say...?
‫أقلت تذكاري؟‬
Indeed, tomorrow is a day to commemorate.
‫سيكون يوم الغد تذكاريًّا فعلًا.‬
Huh?
‫ماذا؟‬
It's a crescent moon tonight.
‫القمر هلال هذه الليلة.‬
Nights like this make my heart race...
‫ليالٍ كهذه تجعل نبضات قلبي تتسارع،‬
and my blood stir...
‫ودمي يثور...‬
K-Klahadore!
‫كـ-كلاهادور-سان!‬
Wh-Why did you break Miss Kaya's gift?!
‫لمَ كسرت هديتها؟‬
A gift? Oh, I'll be accepting a gift, all right...
‫هدية؟ إني أقبل هديةً‬
but not this paltry trinket.
‫ولكن ليس شيئًا كهذا... بل هذا القصر بأكمله!‬
Wh-What are you saying?!
‫مـ-ماذا تقول؟‬
I guess there's no need to continue this charade.
‫لا داعي للاستمرار بالتمثيل.‬
After all, there's going to be an accident in a few hours...
‫ستقع حادثة بعد بضعة ساعات على أيّ حال...‬
It truly has been a long three years!
‫كانت ثلاث سنين طويلة حقًّا!‬
Miss Kaya! Run!
‫اهربي يا آنستي!‬
Captain Jango!
‫قبطان جانغو!‬
It's almost daybreak! Please wake up, Captain Jango!
‫سيبزغ الفجر قريبًا، استيقظ رجاءً أيها القبطان جانغو!‬
Good morning, Captain!
‫صباح الخير يا قبطان!‬
Good morning!
‫صباح الخير!‬
You morons!
‫أيها الحمقى!‬
My policy is to say "good morning" when the sun is up!
‫سياستي هي قول صباح الخير بعد شروق الشمس!‬
Looks like he's in a bad mood.
‫يبدو بمزاج سيّئ.‬
He did just wake up...
‫ذلك لأنه استيقظ توًّا...‬
Look!
‫انظروا!‬
The moon's still up, and it's the middle of the night.
‫لا يزال القمر مرتفعًا وما زلنا في منتصف الليل!‬
How dare you raise your voices!
‫كيف تصرخون هكذا؟!‬
– Our apologies, sir! We're sorry, sir!
‫التمس منا العذر!‬
Alright then, good morning.
‫صباح النور جميعًا!‬
Good morning? That's the opposite of what he just said!
‫صباح النور؟ هذا مغايرٌ لما قاله آنفًا!‬
You idiot! He's in a better mood now, that's all!
‫هذا يعني أن مزاجه تحسّن فحسب أيها الأحمق!‬
Now, men!
‫يا رجال!‬
"One-Two" Jango Acting Captain of the Black Cat Pirates
‫الملقب بـ«جانغو، واحد-اثنان»‬ ‫مُكلف بقيادة قراصنة القط الأسود‬
Set sail!
‫إبحار!‬
– Aye, aye!
‫أجل!‬
Alright! Perfect!
‫حسنٌ، هذا مثالي!‬
They won't be able to climb up this slope anymore...
‫لن يتمكنوا من صعود المنحدر الآن‬
thanks to all the oil we've poured on it!
‫بفضل الزيت الذي سكبناه هنا.‬
We'll attack 'em while they slip and slide around!
‫سنوقعهم عن المنحدر ثم نجهز عليهم.‬
Oil, huh...?
‫زيت إذًا؟‬
No matter what, we will protect this slope!
‫على أيّ حال، سنحمي هذا المنحدر مهما كلّف الأمر!‬
Let's just hope that none of us slip down there.
‫لنأمل ألّا يحدث نقيض ذلك وننزلق بدورنا!‬
It'd be pretty dumb to get caught in our own trap.
‫الوقوع بفخٍ نصبناه بأنفسنا لَحماقةٌ.‬
You sure did come up with a slick plan!
‫تذهلني مقدرتك على التفكير بفعل أشياء لعوبة كهذه!‬
O-Of course!
‫طبعًا أقدر!‬
I have complete confidence in my slingshot and daring ideas!
‫بجرأتي ومقلاعي، يقيني لا يتزعزع!‬
It's almost dawn.
‫يكاد يبزغ الفجر.‬
Any moment now.
‫سيأتون.‬
We're here!
‫وصلنا!‬
Alright!
‫حسنٌ يا رجال، اقتحموا القرية!‬
Captain! There are a couple of strange boats here!
‫أيها القبطان، هناك قاربان مريبان هنا!‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟‬
Should we check 'em out?
‫أأذهب لتفقدهما؟‬
Leave 'em.
‫اتركهما‬
I doubt they've got treasure.
‫وأشك أن فيهما كنزًا‬
Where are they? The sky's all bright now.
‫ألن يأتوا؟ أشرقت الشمس‬
Where could they be?
‫ماذا حصل لهم؟‬
Maybe they overslept or something?
‫ربما استغرقوا في النوم أو شيء كهذا‬
Say...
‫بالمناسبة...‬
Maybe it's just me,
‫أهذه مخيلتي؟‬
but I swear I hear shouting coming from somewhere...
‫أسمع صوتًا!‬
Yeah, I definitely hear something!
‫أسمع صوت حقًّا!‬
N-Now that you mention it...
‫بـ-بالمناسبة...‬
Hey! What is it?!
‫ما الخطب؟‬
There's a place just like this to the north!
‫هناك مكانُ كهذا في الشمال أيضًا!‬
Don't tell me…!
‫لا يمكن...‬
You mean this is the wrong shore?!
‫أتعني أننا في الساحل الخطأ؟‬
This is where they had their secret meeting, so I just assumed...
‫جرى اجتماعهما السري هنا، فافترضتُ ذلك.‬
Hey, hurry! They're gonna reach the village! Where is this place?!
‫لنسرع، سيدخلون القرية! أين ذلك المكان؟‬
If you run straight north from here, you'll get there in three minutes!
‫إن ركضت شمالًا مباشرة من هنا فستصل خلال ثلاث دقائق!‬
It looks basically the same, so we just need to stop them at the slope there!
‫شبيهٌ بهذا المكان، علينا إيقافهم عند المنحدر.‬
Hold on...
‫ماذا؟‬
Oh no!
‫مصيبة!‬
The north shore is where our boats are!
‫الساحل الشمالي هو مكان وجود قاربينا!‬
They'll take our treasure!
‫سيسلبون كنزنا!‬
I'll get there in twenty seconds!
‫سأذهب إلى هناك خلال 20 ثانية!‬
Dammit!
‫سحقًا!‬
My brilliant oil trap was all for nothing!
‫فسدت خطتي العبقريّة خاصتي!‬
My treasure...
‫كنزي...‬
Hey!
‫أنتِ!‬
What're you doing? Let's go!
‫ماذا تفعلين؟ لنذهب!‬
Yeah! We have to hurr–
‫أ-أجل! علينا أن نسر...‬
Help! I'm slipping!
‫ساعدني! سأسقط!‬
Let go, you moron!
‫اتركيني أيتها الحمقاء!‬
Sorry!
‫أعتذر!‬
Perfect!
‫رائع!‬
Thanks, Zoro!
‫شكرًا لك يا زورو.‬
Sorry! The treasure's in danger!
‫معذرةً فالكنز في خطر.‬
Try to get back up somehow!
‫حاول الصعود بطريقةٍ ما.‬
That girl's gonna pay!
‫لن أغفر لتلك المرأة.‬
I won't let them enter the village!
‫لن أسمح لهم بدخول القرية أبدًا!‬
But man, Luffy sure runs fast...!
‫ولكن لوفي سريع حقًّا!‬
I can't even see him anymore!
‫لم أعد أراه‬
Straight north! Straight north! Straight north!
‫شمالًا مباشرة، شمالًا مباشرة، شمالًا مباشرة!‬
They're dead meat if they so much as touch my treasure!
‫لن أغفر لهم إن مسّوا كنزي.‬
Someone's at the top of the slope!
‫هناك أحد على قمة التل!‬
It's you!
‫أنت!‬
My name is Captain Usopp!
‫اسمي هو القبطان أوسوب.‬
I've been waiting for you all this time!
‫كنت بانتظاركم هنا طوال الوقت!‬
Wh-What the...? I'm the first one here?!
‫مـ-ماذا؟ أأنا أول الواصلين؟‬
But he was running way ahead of me!
‫رغم أنه كان يسبقني كثيرًا.‬
Dammit!
‫تبًّا!‬
What do I do?!
‫ماذا عليّ فعله؟‬
I can't climb up!
‫لا أستطيع الصعود!‬
I'm at the village now!
‫بلغت القرية!‬
That's weird!
‫هذا غريب!‬
He said north, so I ran in the coldest direction!
‫قال شمالًا لذا ركضت نحو اتجاه بارد!‬
You're that kid who overheard our plans. What do you think you're doing?
‫أنت ذاك الفتى...‬
I-I'm warning you!
‫أ-أحذركم!‬
Turn back while you still can!
‫عودوا بما أنّ الفرصة سانحة لكم الآن!‬
Or else my crew of 100 million men will beat the crap out of you guys!
‫وإلّا فإنّ رفاقي المئة مليون سيبرحونكم ضربًا!‬
A hundred million?
‫مئة مليون؟‬
Hey now, no one's falling for that!
‫هذه أسوأ من كذبة أطفال!‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟ مئة مليون؟ مذهل!‬
He's obviously lying, Captain!
‫إنّه يكذب طبعًا أيها القبطان!‬
He's so gullible...
‫يا لسذاجته...‬
They saw through it?
‫تبًّا، كشفوني‬
He seriously thought he could fool us, too...
‫ظن أن بإمكانه خداعنا حقًّا!‬
Why, you...!
‫أيها الوغد‬
How dare you trick me!
‫كيف تجرؤ على خداعي؟‬
Captain Jango! I have news!
‫أيها القبطان جانغو! أحملُ خبرًا!‬
Really?! Is it bad?!
‫حقًّا؟ أهوَ تعيس؟‬
No! It's not bad!
‫كلا، ليس كذلك!‬
We found treasure on those strange boats!
‫عثرنا على كنزٍ في تلك القوارب المريبة!‬
Lots of it, too!
‫إنه مقدار مذهل!‬
Maybe four, no, five million berries!
‫ربما أربعة، لا بل خمسة ملايين بيري!‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟‬
F-Five million berries...?!
‫خـ-خمسة ملايين بيري؟‬
Why do those guys have that much money on their boats?
‫لماذا توجد كلّ هذه الأموال في قاربيهم؟‬
So you found my treasure!
‫هذا كنزي!‬
I'll let you have it!
‫ولكن سأعطيه لكم!‬
What?! You'll give us the treasure?!
‫ماذا؟ ستعطينا الكنز؟‬
That's right!
‫كما سمعتم!‬
In exchange, all I ask is that you leave immediately!
‫بمقابل ذلك الكنز، عودوا أدراجكم!‬
Wha...?!
‫ماذا؟‬
Is he really trying to buy us off?
‫أتعتقد أنّ بإمكانك ردعنا مقابل المال؟‬
What a scummy guy!
‫يا لشناءته من تصرف!‬
You fool...
‫أحمق.‬
We're pirates.
‫نحن قراصنة.‬
Of course we're going to take the treasure!
‫سنأخذ الكنز طبعًا!‬
But that's no reason for us to turn back.
‫ولكن ذلك ليس سببًا كافيًا لأن نرجع‬
Y-You have a point...
‫هـ-هذا صحيح...‬
Alright, then! On "one, two, Jango," you'll let us pass!
‫إن فهمت، فافسح لنا الطريق بعد قولي «واحد، اثنان، جانغو»!‬
It's that weapon from before!
‫هذا السلاح من حينها!‬
One...
‫واحد، اثنان...‬
Ja–
‫–جا‬
Quit saying stupid crap!
‫كف عن ترهاتك!‬
Wh-Who's she?!
‫مـ-من هذه المرأة؟‬
Captain! This is no time to hypnotize yourself and let people through!
‫هذا ليس وقت تنويم نفسك مغناطيسيًا وتسمح للناس بالعبور أيها القبطان!‬
The treasure on those boats is mine!
‫كنز ذلك القارب ملك لي!‬
You won't get a single berry!
‫لن أسمح لكم بأخذ ولا حتّى بيري واحد!‬
Hold on to it for me because I'm coming for it!
‫أمسكوا به جيّدًا! سآتي لأخذه الآن!‬
That hurt!
‫هذا مؤلم!‬
Who said you could give them my treasure?!
‫لماذا أعطيتهم كنزي دون إذني؟‬
Well, you didn't have to whack me!
‫لا بأس بقولي لهم ذلك فحسب!‬
What're you talking about?! I just saved you!
‫ماذا تقول بعد أن أنقذتك؟‬
Huh?
‫ماذا؟‬
I forgot to mention, but don't look at his ring when he starts counting!
‫نسيت إخبارك، لا تحدّق بحلقه حتى النهاية!‬
He's a hypnotist!
‫إنّه منوّم مغناطيسي!‬
H-Hypnotist?!
‫مـ-منوّم مغناطيسي؟‬
So, where's Luffy?
‫أين لوفي إذًا؟‬
He got here first, right?
‫أوَليس أول الراكضين؟‬
Dunno!
‫لا أدري، إمّا أنه خاف أو ضلّ الطريق!‬
That'd mean he's lost.
‫ضلّ الطريق إذًا.‬
Man, just when we need him, too!
‫ويحه، كيف له أن يتوه في وقت مهم كهذا؟‬
Alright, I'll take command.
‫سآخذ القيادة هنا.‬
Go kick their butts! I'll cover you!
‫اذهبي لضربهم وسأدعمك!‬
What?! Hold on! Why me?!
‫ماذا؟ لماذا أنا؟‬
There's no way I can take on that huge army!
‫من المستحيل أن أواجه جيشًا ضخمًا كهذا، فأنا ضعيفة!‬
Don't be fooled just 'cause I'm a guy!
‫كوني رجلًا لا يعني أنّي قويّ!‬
I'm so scared that my legs are shaking like crazy! See?!
‫أنا خائف لدرجة أنّ رجلاي ترتعشان بشكلٍ لا يصدق! انظري!‬
Big deal!
‫وما بذلك؟‬
I'm so scared my eyes are tearing up!
‫انظر، أنا خائفة لدرجة أنّ عينَيّ غارقتين بالدموع!‬
Your eyes are bone dry!
‫إنّهما جافتان بالكامل!‬
If you're gonna lie, at least make it believable!
‫إن كنتِ ستكذبين، فاجعليها أكثر واقعيّة!‬
That's rich coming from you!
‫لا أريد سماع هذا منك!‬
We don't have time to deal with this...
‫لا وقت لأن نبعث معهما.‬
Just trample over them and head for the village, men!
‫اسحقوهما فورًا وتقدموا إلى القرية يا رجال!‬
H-Here they come!
‫إ-إنّهم قادمون!‬
Oh, yeah!
‫تذكرت!‬
I have caltrops!
‫لديّ فخاخ شائكة!‬
So you do have some goodies!
‫بحوزتك أشياء جيدة إذًا!‬
Gimme, gimme!
‫أعطني، أعطني!‬
Take this!
‫خذوا هذه!‬
Caltrop Hell!
‫جحيم الفخاخ الشائكة‬ ‫ماكيبيشي جيغوكو‬
Damn you, Nami!
‫سحقًا، تبًّا لنامي!‬
She's gonna pay for this!
‫لن أغفر لها ما حييت!‬
I made it!
‫اجتزته!‬
Wh-Which way is the north shore?!
‫أ-أين هو الطريق شمالًا إلى الساحل؟‬
Straight north! Straight north! Straight north!
‫مباشرة شمالًا، مباشرة شمالًا، مباشرة شمالًا!‬
Which way is north?!
‫أين الشمال؟‬
Oww!
‫مؤلم!‬
Alright! We got 'em!
‫مرحى، نلنا منهم!‬
Now, then...!
‫والآن...‬
Lethal Lead Star!
‫النجم الرئيس الفتاك‬ ‫هيساتسو ناماري بوشي‬
Bastard!
‫وغد!‬
Way to go!
‫أحسنت!‬
Keep it up, now!
‫استمر على هذا المنوال!‬
I'm gonna take a breather.
‫سأنسحب قليلًا.‬
But it hasn't even been five minutes!
‫لم تقاتلي بعد حتّى!‬
Wh-What is it?!
‫ما الخطب؟!‬
There are caltrops behind us too...
‫هناك فخاخ شائكة خلفنا أيضًا...‬
Are you stupid?!
‫أيتها الحمقاء!‬
You dropped 'em there!
‫أنتِ من أسقطتِهم هنا!‬
Outta the damn way!
‫ابتعد عن طريقنا!‬
Do you seriously think you can stop us?
‫أتعتقد أنّ بإمكانك إيقافنا حقًّا؟‬
Let's go, guys!
‫لنذهب جميعًا!‬
Captain Kuro is waiting!
‫القبطان كورو بانتظارنا.‬
– Yeah!
‫هيّا!‬
Wh-What the...?!
‫مـ-ما خطبه؟‬
Let go, you bastard! Dammit, let go!
‫اتركني أيها الوغد! اتركني!‬
Damn you!
‫أيها الوغد!‬
Take this! You bastard!
‫أيها الوغد! أيها الوغد!‬
I... can't...
‫لا يمكنني...‬
let you get past this slope.
‫أن أسمح لكم بالعبور من هذا المنحدر...‬
This is just another one of my lies...
‫لأنّي كذبت كالعادة...‬
so it'll be just another ordinary day for the village.
‫ستحظى القرية بيومٍ عادي آخر فحسب...‬
I absolutely will not let you pass!
‫لذلك لن أسمح لكم بالعبور أبدًا!‬
Damn brat! Shut up!
‫اصمت أيها الطفل اللعين!‬
You bitch!
‫أيتها المرأة الشقيّة!‬
Oww!
‫مؤلم!‬
Are you...?!
‫أنتِ...‬
That's enough now!
‫هذا يكفي!‬
Hey, you guys!
‫يا جماعة!‬
Quit bothering with them and get going already!
‫لا تبالوا بهما واذهبوا فورًا!‬
Have you forgotten this is Captain Kuro's plan?!
‫هل نسيتم أنّ هذه خطّة القبطان كورو؟‬
If anything derails it,
‫إن أفسدتم الخطة،‬
he'll kill every last one of us!
‫فسنُقتل جميعًا!‬
Do you understand that, you dumbasses?!
‫أتفهمون هذا أيها الحمقى؟‬
W-Well, uh...
‫أ-أنتم...‬
Yeah, let's hurry to the village!
‫أجل، لنسرع إلى القرية!‬
Stop...
‫ا-انتظروا...‬
Dammit...
‫سحقًا...‬
Stop!
‫انتظر!‬
Stop... Don't go to the village!
‫انتظر... لا تذهبوا إلى القرية!‬
Shut up!
‫اصمت!‬
Stop!
‫توقفوا!‬
Please...!
‫أترجاكم...‬
Please don't kill everyone!
‫لا تقتلوا الجميع...!‬
I love this village!
‫أحب هذه القرية!‬
I want to protect it!
‫أريد حمايتها!‬
Wh-What is this, Captain Jango?!
‫مـ-ما هذا أيها القبطان جانغو؟‬
Nobody said the village had guys like these!
‫لم أسمع وجود أُناس كهذَيْنِ في القرية!‬
About time...
‫وصلا أخيرًا...‬
Why the hell are these guys such pushovers?!
‫ما هؤلاء الضعفاء؟‬
Beats me!
‫لا أدري!‬
I'm not satisfied either!
‫لا يروقني الأمر!‬
Nami! I can't believe you kicked me down the slope!
‫كيف تجرؤين على ركلي هناك يا نامي؟‬
Usopp, you jerk!
‫أوسوب أيها الوغد!‬
You didn't say which way was north!
‫لم تخبرني أين كان الشمال!‬
Who are these guys?
‫من هذان؟‬
They're late...
‫تأخروا...‬
I thought they knew full well what happens to those who derail my plans.
‫ظننتُهم يدركون مصيرَ من يعيق خططي.‬
Taking their sweet time like this...
‫كيف يجرؤون على التباطؤ...‬
Well, if they've forgotten even that…
‫إن كانوا نسوا ذلك،‬
then I'll slaughter them all!
‫فسأقتلهم جميعًا!‬
Y-You guys are that strong?!
‫أ-أنتما بهذه القوة؟‬
What took you guys so long?!
‫تأخرتما في الوصول!‬
You're the one who got me stuck back there!
‫أنتِ من أوقعتني هناك!‬
I didn't mean to, okay?! I didn't have a choice!
‫كانت تلك حادثة! ما باليد حيلة!‬
Besides, one of us getting free was better than both of us staying stuck.
‫نجاةُ أحدنا خيرٌ من هلاكنا.‬
Then you should've stayed!
‫كان الأحرى أن تَبقي إذًا!‬
Seriously!
‫كيف لي أن أعرف أيّ اتجاه هو الشمال من غيره؟‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟‬
You're the one who ran off all confident!
‫أنت من انطلق راكضًا بكل ثقة!‬
Well, I was just trying to help you.
‫انطلقت لاشعوريًا.‬
Night is long gone now...
‫انقضى الليل تمامًا الآن...‬
and Captain Kuro has a short temper...
‫والقبطان كورو لا يتحمل التأخير.‬
Hey, men!
‫يا رجال!‬
Don't tell me you couldn't handle two measly brats!
‫أيُعقل أنّ هذين الطّفلين قد قضيا عليكم؟‬
Listen!
‫اسمعوا،‬
We don't have time to be dilly-dallying here!
‫لا وقت للتسكع هنا طوال اليوم!‬
If our enemy is strong, we just need to be even stronger!
‫إن كان خصمنا قويًّا، فعلينا أن نصير أقوى!‬
Now watch this ring closely!
‫هيّا، راقبوا هذا الحلق جيّدًا!‬
On "one, two, Jango," you guys will grow strong.
‫عندما أقول «واحد، اثنان، جانغو»، ستصيرون أقوياء‬
Your wounds will completely heal, and you will grow stronger and stronger!
‫ستشفى جراحكم بالكامل، وتصيرون أقوى فأقوى!‬
What are they doing?
‫ماذا يفعلون؟‬
It's hypnosis!
‫إنه تنويم مغناطيسي،‬
He's trying to convince them to be stronger!
‫يحاول أن يقنعهم أن يصيروا أقوى‬
How ridiculous!
‫يا للسخافة!‬
One...
‫واحد!‬
two...
‫اثنان!‬
Jango!
‫جانغو!‬
No way!
‫لا يعقل!‬
H-He destroyed part of the cliff!
‫حـ-حطّم المنحدر!‬
Talk about power!
‫يا للقوة!‬
That's some effective hypnosis!
‫نُوّموا مغناطيسيًا حقًّا!‬
With an army that strong...
‫بوجود هذا العدد الغفير منهم بهذه القوّة...‬
Go!
‫انطلقوا!‬
Crush anyone who gets in the way!
‫اسحقوا أيًّا من يعترض طريقكم!‬
Get back, you guys!
‫تراجعا!‬
We'll handle this!
‫سنتولى هذا!‬
Hey, Luffy!
‫يا لوفي...‬
Luffy?!
‫لوفي؟‬
You got hypnotized too?!
‫نُوّمتَ مغناطيسيًا أيضًا؟‬
He's so simple-minded...!
‫ما أبسط عقله!‬
Gum-Gum...
‫غومو غومو نو‬ ‫فاكهة المطاط‬
Gatling!
‫المدفع الرشاش‬ ‫غاتلينغ‬
Damn you, Captain Kuro...
‫تبًّا لك أيها القبطان كورو...‬
Thinking he'd have no impact was a mistake!
‫كنت مخطئًا أنه لن يحدث أيّ تأثير!‬
They're no ordinary brats!
‫هؤلاء ليسوا مجرد أطفال عاديين!‬
Where's he off to now?!
‫إلى أين سيذهب؟‬
What's he gonna do?!
‫ماذا سيفعل؟‬
Go, Luffy!
‫انطلق يا لوفي!‬
He's gonna destroy the ship!
‫سيحطّم السفينة!‬
No, he's not!
‫كلّا!‬
He's gonna crush us with it!
‫إنّه ينوي سحقنا بهذا.‬
Please do something, Captain!
‫أرجوك تصرَّف أيها القبطان.‬
On "one, two, Jango," you'll get sleepy!
‫نم عندما أقول «واحد، اثنان، جانغو»!‬
One...
‫واحد!‬
two...
‫اثنان!‬
Jango!
‫جانغو!‬
Looks like they're just about wiped out!
‫يبدو أنه هزمهم تقريبًا.‬
I'd say so.
‫نعم.‬
Hey!
‫الأهمّ، لوفي عالق هناك!‬
He won't die.
‫لن يموت.‬
Just worry about your own wounds.
‫اقلق على إصاباتك‬
Damn that brat!
‫فعلها ذلك الطفل!‬
Now the plan is all but ruined!
‫أُفسدت الخطة بالكامل الآن!‬
If Captain Kuro saw this,
‫إن رأى القبطان كورو هذا،‬
he'd slaughter all of us too!
‫فسيقتلنا جميعًا أيضًا!‬
Hey, Buchi!
‫يا بوتشي!‬
Come look at this mess!
‫انظر لهذا، يا لجلله من أمر!‬
What the hell?!
‫ما هذا؟‬
We still have our trump card!
‫ما زال لدينا ورقة رابحة!‬
Come forth, Meowban Brothers!
‫تعاليا أيها الأخوان مياوبان!‬
It is Klahadore from the mansion!
‫إنه كلاهادور خادم القصر فعلًا،‬
Why is he heading for the shore so early...?!
‫لِمَ يسير نحو الساحل في هذا الصباح الباكر؟‬
As a kid, I had a dream of a dazzling treasure
‫عِندما كُنتُ طفلاً صغيرًا،‬
I had a map in my head that I knew would lead me
‫كانت لديَّ رؤيا عن خريطة كنز‬
Charted a course all on my own, so nobody would beat me
‫ولطالما بحثت عن ذلك المكان العجيب‬
The promised land was in my hand, drew a line in the sand
‫قبل أن يهزمني شخصٌ ما ويسبقني إليه‬
My one ambition's slipping right through my hands
‫إذا كانَ العالم سيتغيّر‬
But if the world ever changes I'll call out your name
‫قبل أن أتمكن من تحقيق حُلمي‬
We could return to a time when our lives were still the same
‫في تلك الحال ارجع بالزمن للوقت الذي لم أعلم به عن شيء‬
Take me to the place where memories remain
‫حتّى لا تتلاشى ذكرياتي‬